index.md 11/24/2020

Contact Information

Alana Kaffenberger

Phone: (423) 366-2338

Email: akkaffenberger@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Enthusiastic student currently studying Neuroscience on a pre-med track. Strong multitasking and problem-solving skills with ability to work with minimal supervision. Academic experience in many lab environments including: General Chemistry, Organic Chemistry, Intro to Neuroscience Techniques, and Cell Biology.

Education

University of Kentucky

- Bachelor of Science in Neuroscience, Pre-Med (3.70 GPA)
- Lewis Honors College
- Graduation Date: December 2021

Work Experience

Brand Associate—Old Navy

July 2020 - Present

- Greeted customers, responded to concerns, and ensured consistent customer engagement
- Achieved goals set on daily basis
- Restored and maintained orderly appearance of main floor
- Managed financial transactions

After School Counselor—Cassidy Elementary School

January 2019 - March 2020

- Supervised children ages 5-11
- · Conducted proper time management
- · Implemented conflict management
- Practiced proper communication skills with children, coworkers, and parents

YMCA Assistant Director—Whitaker >

May 2019 - August 2019

index.md 11/24/2020

- Gained valuable leadership experience
- Adapted to dynamic roles throughout the summer depending on demand
- Expanded communication skills by communicating to and between coworkers, campers, and parents
- Implemented behavior management skills with campers

YMCA Camp Counselor—Whitaker >

May 2018 – August 2018

- Successfully communicated with children, coworkers, and parents
- Gained valuable multitasking and leadership skills
- Guided, encouraged, and monitored children throughout the day with various activities such as: swimming, crafts, reading/spelling, games
- Conducted conflict management with parents and children
- Maintained composure in chaotic environments